Eng: B1-B2


7h00 : go to work.
8h00 : arrive - push up.
10h30: push up.
11h50: have a lunch, must be rice.
13h00: take a nap.
14h00: gogogo.
16h30: push up.
17h00: take a light meal.
18h30: gegege..
20h00: arrive - take a shower - dinner time
21h00: English for life
22h30: Coursera or learn sth new.
0h00 : Doto time? you better sleep
6h00 : Day stalking, night walking, push up, pull up.

and be with my love all days.

Massgo T5


No one has ever seen the face hidden beneath the mask of Yurnero the Juggernaut. 
It is only speculation that he even has one. For defying a corrupt lord, 
Yurnero was exiled from the ancient Isle of Masks--a punishment that saved his life. 
The isle soon after vanished beneath the waves in a night of vengeful magic. 
He alone remains to carry on the Isle's long Juggernaut tradition, 
one of ritual and swordplay. The last practitioner of the art, 
Yurnero's confidence and courage are the result of endless practice; 
his inventive bladework proves that he has never stopped challenging himself. 
Still, his motives are as unreadable as his expression. 
For a hero who has lost everything twice over, 
he fights as if victory is a foregone conclusion.

Chưa một ai có thể thấy được những gì ẩn đằng sau chiếc mặt nạ của Yurnero of the Juggernaunt.
Nhiều lời đồn đoán rằng đó là một gương mặt u uất. Do chống lại vị lãnh chúa tàn bạo, Yurnero bị kết tội
và đày ải đến vùng đất cổ xưa Isle of Mask - sự trừng phạt vô tình đã cứu mạng một vị anh hùng. Rất mau sau đó,
hòn đảo đã biến mất cùng với sự gào thét của những con sóng giận giữ trong một đêm đầy những phép thuật
của hận thù. Yur là người còn lại cuối cùng để tiếp tục duy trì các nghi thức về kiếm thuật, một trong những
truyền thống lâu đời của các Juggernaunt. Là truyền nhân cuối cùng của kiếm đạo, bộ óc lạnh lùng và trái tim
quả cảm của ông là kết quả của những năm tháng luyện tập không có hồi kết. Yur không ngừng thách thức và đặt giới hạn mới
cho bản thân để đạt đến cảnh giới thoát tục và kỹ năng thượng thừa. Trải qua hàng nghìn năm, động lực
cũng như con người của ông vẫn đang còn là một bí ẩn. Người ta suy đoán rằng, với một vị anh hùng đã mất
tất cả đến hai lần trong đời, ông ấy chiến đấu như một kết cục tất yếu cho chiến thắng.

Sven is the bastard son of a Vigil Knight, born of a Pallid Meranth, 
raised in the Shadeshore Ruins. 
With his father executed for violating the Vigil Codex, 
and his mother shunned by her wild race, 
Sven believes that honor is to be found in no social order--but only in himself. 
After tending his mother through a lingering death, he offered 
himself as a novice to the Vigil Knights, 
never revealing his identity. For thirteen years he studied in his father's school, 
mastering the rigid code that declared his existence an abomination. 
Then, on the day that should have been his In-Swearing, he seized 
the Outcast Blade, 
shattered the Sacred Helm, and burned the Codex in the Vigil's Holy Flame. 
He strode from Vigil Keep, 
forever solitary, following his private code to the last strict rune. 
Still a knight, yes...but a Rogue Knight.

Sven là một đứa con ngỗ nghịch của Vigil Knight, sinh ra ở Pallid Meranth 
và lớn lên từ vùng Shadeshore Ruins. Sinh ra trong 1 gia đình có người cha bị xử tử
vì phạm luật của Vigil, cùng người mẹ bị xa lánh bởi vẻ hoang dã của mình, Sven bắt
đầu tin rằng, danh vọng không thể tìm thấy bằng trật tự xã hội mà chỉ bằng tự lực bản thân
Sau khi chăm sóc mẹ cho đến những giây phút cuối đời của bà, Sven che dấu thân phận và tình nguyện trở thành
1 tín đồ của Vigil Knights. Trong suốt 13 năm theo học trong ngôi trường của cha,
người ta xem sự tồn tại của Sven là 1 điều kinh tởm. Nhưng, trong cái hôm mà lẽ ra đã trở thành
lễ tuyên thệ của mình, sven đã cướp lấy thanh Outcast Blade, đập vỡ Sacred Helm và 
đốt cháy bộ luật Codex trong ngọn lửa thần thánh của Vigrl. Sven bước ra khỏi Vigil, luôn
luôn cô độc, tuân theo luật của riêng mình. Sven vẫn là một Knight, nhưng là Rouge Knight

The remote village of Pole had no knowledge of the wars raging in 
the heart of the kingdom. For them, the quiet of spear fishing, 
and a family meal were all that a full life required. 
Yet war came for them nonetheless. 
Joining the able-bodied conscripts as they filed passed their homes, 
the humble lancer Azwraith vowed to bring peace to his kingdom, 
and in so doing, his people. Placed with his kin in the 
vanguard of the final assault against the Dread Magus Vorn, 
the cost to his fellows was absolute. 
As the charging force battled toward the fortress, 
Azwraith alone among his kind remained standing, 
and he alone was able to infiltrate the keep. 
Focused and infuriated by the slaughter of his brothers, 
Azwraith bested each of the wizard's deadly traps and conjured guardians. 
Soon the simple fisherman arrived at Vorn's tower sanctum. 
The pair dueled through the night, pike to staff, as chaos raged below, 
and with a deafening cry Azwraith pierced his enemy. 
But the wizard did not simply expire; 
he exploded into uncountable shards of light, 
penetrating his killer with power. 
As the dust settled and the smoke of combat began to clear, 
Azwraith found himself standing among a throng of his kin. 
Each seemed to be dressed as he was, each seemed armed as he was, 
and he could sense that each thought as he did.
Aware that his allies were approaching, he willed these 
phantoms to hide themselves, and one by one they began to 
vanish into nothingness. As the soldiers came upon the sanctum, 
they found the warrior that had bested the wizard. 
When they approached their champion, the lancer vanished. 
The pikeman who had stood before them was no more than another phantom.

Những người dân ở ngôi làng phía bắc bao đời nay vốn không có kiến thức về
chiến tranh đã nổi giận trong trái tim của vương quốc. Đối với họ, những cần
câu cá yên tĩnh và thức ăn dành cho gia đình là tất cả những gì cần cho cuộc sống.
Chiến tranh đến với họ theo 1 cách vô nghĩa nhất.
Gia nhập theo lời tổng động viên và được ghi danh vào đoàn quân ra trận,
Anh chàng kị binh tầm thường Azwraith tuyên thệ rằng sẽ mang lại hòa bình cho
đất nước, cho người dân của mình. Đóng quân và tham gia vào đội quân tiên phong
trong cuộc đột kích cuối cùng nhắm vào Dread Magus Vorn, các chiến hữu của
Azwraith lần lượt nằm xuống là 1 điều k thể tránh khỏi. Với trọng trách phải đánh chiếm
pháo đài, Azwraith là chiến binh cuối cùng trong đội quân còn sót lại xâm nhập được vào thành.
Căm phẫn trước cảnh tượng những người anh em của mình bị tàn sát đẫm máu, Azwraith phá hủy và tiêu diệt
bất cứ những cái bẫy ma thuật và những tên cận vệ ma quỷ. Cuối cùng anh chàng câu cá hiền hòa đã
tiến đến cung điện và đối mặt với Vorn. Cuộc đối đầu diễn ra xuyên màn đêm, giữa ngọn giáo và phép trượng 
cùng với tất cả sự phẫn nộ và hỗn độn, và cuối cùng phát lên 1 tiếng khóc kinh hoàng, Azwraith đã
đâm xuyên ngực kẻ thù của anh. Nhưng phép thuật hắc ám không dễ bị giải trừ như thế. Hắn nổ tung
thành vô số những mảnh ánh sáng nhỏ li ti, xuyên buốt thấu qua người đã hạ sát hắn với nguồn 
năng lượng kinh người. Cho đến khi những hạt cát đã lắng đọng xuống đất và cột khói chiến tranh cũng
ngừng bốc. Azwraith thức tỉnh và nhận ra mình đang bị bao bọc với những người đồng đội chung quanh.
Mỗi người đều có lối phục sức giống như anh, cầm trên tay những binh khí như anh, và cũng cảm nhận được những
gì mà anh cảm thấy. Nhận ra rằng đồng minh của mình đang tiến đến, Azwraith xua bầy bóng ma tự dấu mình đi, 
từng bóng một dần dần tan biến theo một kiểu vô nghĩa lạ lùng. Lúc mọi người đặt chân vào cung điện, họ nhận
ra rằng người chiến binh đã đánh bại tất cả mọi phép thuật, lúc họ tiến đến người anh hùng của mình, Azwraith dần dần tan biến.
Chàng kị sỹ đứng trước mắt họ đã không còn gì ngoài những bóng ma khác.

Vào thuở sơ khai, người ta quan niệm rằng, 
phép thuật là nghệ thuật đầu tiên của trí óc
Nó không đòi hỏi công nghệ, không cần đũa phép
hay những trang bị phù phép ngoài một trí óc vĩ đại.
Tất cả những những cuốn trap về nghi lễ chỉ là một hình thức để ghi nhớ.
và nó có tác dụng gợi nhớ lại các thể cách để giải phóng sức mạnh của phép thuật.
Pháp sư vĩ đại nhất thời bấy giờ là người có một bộ óc vĩ dại, tất nhiên.
...
Nhưng trong số những người tập sự phép thuật, có một trường hợp ngoại lệ.
một thiên tài bởi trí thông minh tuyệt đỉnh và trí nhớ phi thường - người được
biết đến với cái tên Invoker. Tài năng của Invoker nở rộ từ lúc còn trẻ, độ tuổi
mà anh ta đã có thể biết đến không dưới 10 câu phép thuật. và sử dụng chúng 1 cách tức thì
In its earliest, and some would say most potent form, 
magic was primarily the art of memory. 
It required no technology, no wands or appurtenances 
other than the mind of the magician. 
All the trappings of ritual were merely mnemonic devices, 
meant to allow the practitioner 
to recall in rich detail the specific mental formulae 
that unlocked a spell's power. The greatest mages in those days
were the ones blessed with the greatest memories, 
and yet so complex were the invocations 
that all wizards were forced to specialize. 
The most devoted might hope in a lifetime 
to have adequate recollection of three spells—four at most. 
Ordinary wizards were content to know two, 
and it was not uncommon for a 
village mage to know only one—with even that 
requiring him to consult grimoires as an aid against 
forgetfulness on the rare occasions 
when he might be called to use it. 
But among these early practitioners there was one exception, 
a genius of vast intellect and prodigious memory 
who came to be known as the Invoker. In his youth, 
the precocious wizard mastered not four, not five, 
not even seven incantations: He could command no fewer than ten spells, 
and cast them instantly. Many more he learned but found 
useless, and would practice once then purge from his mind 
forever, to make room for more practical invocations. 
One such spell was the Sempiternal 
Cantrap—a longevity spell of such power that 
those who cast it in the world's first days are 
among us still (unless they have been crushed to atoms). 
Most of these quasi-immortals live quietly, 
afraid to admit their secret: 
But Invoker is not one to keep his gifts hidden. 
He is ancient, learned beyond all others, 
and his mind somehow still has space to contain an 
immense sense of his own worth...as well as the 
Invocations with which he amuses himself through 
the long slow twilight of the world's dying days.

Bất cứ một pháp sư nào cũng có thể thi triển 1 hoặc hai loại phép thuật, và
một số ít mới có thể học hỏi trong một thời gian dài để triwr thành 1 thầy pháp sư
, nhưng chỉ có 1 người tài giỏi nhất mới có thể được gọi là Magus. 

Any mage can cast a spell or two, and a few may even study long enough 
to become a wizard, but only the most talented are allowed to be recognized 
as a Magus. Yet as with any sorcerer’s circle, a sense of community has 
never guaranteed competitive courtesy. Already a renowned duelist and scholar 
of the grander world of sorcery, it had never occurred to Rubick that 
he might perhaps be Magus material until he was in the midst of his seventh 
assassination attempt. As he casually tossed the twelfth of a string of 
would-be killers from a high balcony, it dawned on him how utterly 
unimaginative the attempts on his life had become. Where once the interruption 
of a fingersnap or firehand might have put a cheerful spring in his step, 
it had all become so very predictable. He craved greater competition. 
Therefore, donning his combat mask, he did what any wizard seeking to ascend 
the ranks would do: he announced his intention to kill a Magus.
Rubick quickly discovered that to threaten one Magus is to threaten them all, 
and they fell upon him in force. Each antagonist's spell was an unstoppable 
torrent of energy, and every attack a calculated killing blow. 
But very soon something occurred that Rubick's foes found unexpected: 
their arts appeared to turn against them. Inside the magic maelstrom, 
Rubick chuckled, subtly reading and replicating the powers of one in order to cast
 it against another, sowing chaos among those who had allied against him. 
 Accusations of betrayal began to fly, and soon the sorcerers turned one 
 upon another without suspecting who was behind their undoing.
When the battle finally drew to a close, all were singed and frozen, 
soaked and cut and pierced. More than one lay dead by an ally’s craft. 
Rubick stood apart, sore but delighted in the week’s festivities. 
None had the strength to argue when he presented his petition of 
assumption to the Hidden Council, and the Insubstantial Eleven agreed 
as one to grant him the title of Grand Magus.

Người cựu binh của vô số trận chiến ở hàng ngàn thế giới, Chaos Knight hiện thân
từ hành tinh xa xôi nơi mà những luật lệ của vũ trụ được hình thành. Trong số những
nguyên tố cổ xưa, Chaos già nhất và Chaos liên tục không ngừng nghỉ để tìm kiếm Ánh Sáng.
Rất lâu về trước, the Litght đã đánh bạo ra khỏi vùng đất của tổ tiên, với sự bất chấp hiệp
ước cổ xưa. Ngày nay, Chaos Knight nhảy từ hành tinh này sang hành tinh khác, luôn luôn săn
tìm để dập tắt ánh sáng bất cứ lúc nào hắn bắt gặp. Đã hơn 1 nghìn lần hắn dập tắt nguồn sáng, 
và lại bắt đầu trượt sang hành tinh khác để bát đầu 1 cuộc tìm kiếm mới.
Cưỡi trên mình con chiến mã Armagedon, lao vào chiến trường với sự điên cuồng hỗn độn,


The veteran of countless battles on a thousand worlds, Chaos Knight hails from 
a far upstream plane where the fundamental laws of the universe have found 
sentient expression. Of all the ancient Fundamentals, he is the oldest and most 
tireless—endlessly searching out a being he knows only as “The Light.” 
Long ago the Light ventured out from the progenitor realm, in defiance of 
the first covenant. Now Chaos Knight shifts from plane to plane, always on the 
hunt to extinguish the Light wherever he finds it. A thousand times he has 
snuffed out the source, and always he slides into another plane to continue 
his search anew.
Upon his steed Armageddon he rides, wading into battle with maniacal frenzy, 
drawing strength from the disorder of the universe. A physical manifestation 
of chaos itself, in times of need he calls upon other versions of himself 
from other planes, and together these dark horsemen ride into battle, 
as unstoppable as any force of nature. Only when the last Light of the world 
is scoured from existence will the search be ended. Where rides the Chaos Knight, 
death soon follows.

Nothing is known of Enigma’s background. There are only stories and legends, 
most of them apocryphal, passed down through the ages. In truth, Enigma is a mystery 
for whom the only true biography is description: he is a universal force, a consumer of worlds. 
He is a being of the void, at times corporeal, other times ethereal. A beast between the planes.
There are stories that say he was once a great alchemist who tried to unlock the secrets 
of the universe and was cursed for his arrogance. Other legends tell that he is an ancient 
being of strange gravity, the abyss personified—a twisted voice from out the original 
darkness, before the first light in the universe. And there are older legends that say 
he is the first collapsed star, a black hole grown complicated and sentient—his motivations unknowable, 
his power inexorable, a force of destruction unleashed upon existence itself.